qqclubs.com 2015-11-14

# Privacy Policy - The very best in online Sports Betting, Live Casino, Slots Games and 4D can be found at qqclubs.com | 100% Welcome Bonus

This privacy policy covers QQclubs.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect from you when you access this website, or contact us requesting information, services, or customer support. By "personally identifiable information", we mean your name, address, telephone number(s), email address, identification numbers, identification documentation, and banking information. This policy also applies to QQclubs.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to people that we do not employ or manage.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By accessing and using this website you are deemed to accept the Terms of Use of our Privacy Policy. 

### Information Collection and Use

We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you submit a form on our site, email or write to us requesting information or services or customer support. We may also receive personally identifiable information from you when you use our products and services or from our business partners. We do not collect any personally identifiable information when you are on our site before you login, contact us or submit a form. We only use personally identifiable information to fulfil your requests for information or to render products or services to you.

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identiﬁcation information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit and register on our Site, perform fund transactions, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, ﬁll out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for their name, email address, phone number, and a valid mailing address when necessary. The following information will be collected only by voluntary submission. Users may refuse to supply personally identiﬁcation information, however it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-Personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identiﬁcation information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identiﬁcation information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers' utilized and other similar information.

### Web Browser Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to notify you when cookies are being sent. However, in doing so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How We Use Collected Information

  * **To improve customer service**  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efﬁciently.
  * **To personalise user experience**  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * **To improve our Site**  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **To process funds**  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when we process any funds in our Site. We do not share this information with third parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
Emails may be used to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails such as news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from our mailing list, we include instructions in each mail.

### How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

### Protection Of Minors

Protecting the privacy of minors is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we know who are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. We encourage Users to utilise ﬁltering programs and applications to prevent minors from accessing inappropriate contents on the Internet.

### Changes to This Policy

QQclubs.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modiﬁcations.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people only when:

  * we have your consent to share the information; or
  * we need to share your information to provide the service or product you have requested; or
  * we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of our company to provide a service requested by you (unless we otherwise notify you when we collect such information, these companies shall not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond that which is reasonably necessary to assist us with responding to your request); or
  * we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * we find that your actions on our web sites violate the terms of service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific services.

In order to provide the information or services you have requested from us, we may transfer or store your personally identifiable information on computer equipment or in offices that are located across countries or jurisdictions, and may be managed and processed by our company internally as we please, and you are deemed to consent to the same.

### Contacting Us

If you have any queries about your personally identifiable information we hold, or you wish that information to be updated or deleted, please send an email to cs@qqclubs.com or write to us at the address mentioned in the [contact us](http://qqclubs.com/contact/) section of this web site.
